Da-dad.
Alright, I'm quiet.
Da-dad!
I'm here, honey.
What you doin', Willow?
One two three.
There you go.
With a little pee-pee.
There go, umm go.
Ohh-na. Goo-na.
Everything's OK.
Don't drink your own piss, Willow.
Don't.. eat your own shit.
Even if it's recycled.
Even if, it doesn't look like
piss, or shit,
any more.
It's called a taboo.
Ta..
boo...
Ta.. boo...
Claim me, my little package.
So.. taboo, taboo, taboo.
Yes it is for me.
But not for you, but not for you...
Not for you.
Speed little girl.
If my old man could see me now...
"Break the laws of nature..
"and you'll pay for it..
you little son of a bitch."
You little son of a bitch.
Wait for me!
Waait!
Come on!
Waait, wait for me!
Willow..
♪ Where are you hiding? ♪
In the speckled shade,
from the depths of the tree.
Spiders and centipedes,
crawl across your hands,
above your knees..
♪ Willow ♪
Have to go and feed the dog.
ID 149, reporting.
I removed the defective section
of the external magnetic panel
and replaced it with the one
of my own making.
To save it on electric energy, I've decided
to jettison everything unnecessary..
Fully aware of the consequences.
The child's in good health
and ahh, so am I.
My bloodwork's normal,
my eyesight's stable, know it.
Even if I don't see me, play
this message for.. a hundred years.
Okay. Over and out.
So light Mink.
Barely there.
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon.
C'mon, c'mon. C'mon..
So many tears in such
just a tiny little body!
Stop it pully, please please
stop it stop it, please.
Please it's gonna kill me.
It's gonna kill me.
Please!
OK?
I'm afraid, Willow.
Uhh I could have just drowned you
like a kitten.
Could be so easy.
Should be your first, then me.
These fucking images from Earth.
I can't believe, still make it here..
After all this time.
Looks like..
viruses..
chasing after us.
Parasites.
I'm holdin' on.
Help..
Never caved-in.
I'll hold up.
She's mine.
I'm hers.
It's fucked.
Since we left the solar system,
radio silent.
Nothing...
Those.. random.. images.
Maybe they were programmed,
to keep us on a leash.
Make us believe a return
was possible.
We invented rituals.
Hygiene first.
Here.
Kali Yuga the final,
the final age of man.
Did you know that, I still have
leopards on the street where I live?
Professor, I'm surprised
you've accepted an invitation
to attend a conference
in such a cold country.
Why made you leave
your Assamese hills
and say "yes"?
Curiosity.
But you have a more serious reason
for coming, don't you?
Yes.
Yes indeed.
Radical experiments are taking place
in outer space.
Death row inmates are selected
to be used as guinea pigs.
Is this really how
Occidental governmental authorities
hope to deal with criminals?
I doubt very much.
I mean, they're not being
told the truth about...
What about?
That they will never come back.
We can't even contact them.
Their messages and reports
now take years to get back to us.
We'll be bone dust,
while they're still hurtling
through space.
Up.
C'mon!
Hup!
We're scrap.
Trash.
Refuse that didn't
fit in to persist.
Someone had the bright idea
of recycling us.
Some of us got, life sentences.
Some of us were on death row.
Agency made us an offer:
To serve science.
Given our ages,
how could we say "no"?
At that point, we'd only left
the solar system for three years.
Almost all of us were still alive.
Constant acceleration
creates artificial gravity,
freeing us from
the discomfort of weightlessness.
Body handles it better.
I don't want a sedative.
You put too much in the water
as it is.
Well you got me, juicy peach.
You lied to us.
And you knew it.
You knew it.
Fucking "second chance" doctor.
When I first saw you, you were
a filthy little crackhead.
Look now at you.
Fine specimen.
Fucking child murderer.
Oh so you do have a nervous system.
Eh, look at her!
Look because you're
fucking killing her!
Ohh, calm down!
Did you realise nothing's
ever grow inside of us?
Oh! Behaviour!
Fuck off.
Fucking whore.
Hey. Hm mmh.
It's dirty. It's dirty.
Hmmh, it's our first strawberry.
Ready? Hrrrrh..
Hold on tight.
Hold on tight c'mere.
C'mon. Hey!
Dr. Dibs,
struggling to harvest healthy foetuses,
ones that will survive childbirth.
The guys were in it for the fix.
Wha' about my treat?
Smashin'.
Thank you.
Why do you keep taking their sperm?
Even if you manage to inseminate
one of the girls,
the babies die from radiation.
The odds are not in our favour,
but when my work is accomplished,
when perfection is achieved...
Then what?
Fly away?
Except for me.
I kept my fluids to myself.
She thought she was
doin' me a favour.
Someday...
She was cocky that way.
Doesn't seem to be doing
you much good.
Better than you think.
God, so humiliating!
You need to wipe your nose.
I know I look like a witch.
I mean you all call me Vultura, right?
You're foxy and you know it.
I just don't understand how you can,
still believe in your class II mission?
It's like you become,
the Shaman of Sperm.
It's just a new religion for you.
Because I'm totally devoted
to reproduction.
Happy monk.
Going to sow your fields?
Focking cock-block.
Like everyone, I'd used the Box.
But as time passed I chose,
abstinence over indulgence.
Chastity was a way
of making myself stronger.
Mr. Bluenuts.
This monk thing you got goin' on.
It's cool huh?
So vain!
Wouldn't bet on that.
I like it here.
This reminds me of juvi.
Reminds me of jail.
Same thing as the army.
I get why you choose abstinence.
Masturbate you can,
you can do it out to death.
This fuck-box..
Jesus, that's
a whole 'nother rabbit-hole.
You use it.
I made my wife promise
to raise our son gently.
One thing makes me happy is knowin'
he's gonna be alright.
Your son is old now.
Or he's dead.
This little garden,
is teaching me to enjoy the present.
Nothing else really matters.
Tcherny can't be
your real name, right?
Nah, one of the Russian crew
instructors gave it to me.
Think it mean "black" but...
who knows, ehh?
What's "Monte"?
Your folks Italian or somethin'?
I was raised by my dog.
I'm tired as bat.
I'll just flyin' around.
I can't do this space shit no more.
At 99% of the speed of light,
the entire sky converged
before our eyes.
The sensation,
moving backwards, even though
we're moving forwards,
getting further
from what's getting nearer,
sometimes I just can't stand it.
According to Dibs,
captain
is ill-equipped
for this stress.
Bad genes.
Leukaemia has invaded his body.
His eyes are more sensitive
to the radiation than ours.
Everything he sees
is bathed in, a black halo.
I have good genes.
Well...
Get out of it!
Be careful with her!
We were at the halfway point.
Four more years to our destination.
We had to begin the deceleration manoeuvre
so the ship would approach a black hole.
One of the closest in our galaxy.
Small.
This was the main goal
of our mission.
Our Class 1 suicide ride.
To check if we could capture
a black hole's rotating energy.
And we - "heroes" -
would provide humanity with
almost boundless resources.
There Penrose process.
I want to fuck you.
Stinks.
The usual stench.
It gets me hard.
Tcherny decided to start
sleeping in the garden.
I'm glad I'm so weak.
I'm so happy I'm haemorrhaging.
Be quiet.
Stop lying to yourself.
One day, it'll happen to you.
You're not as strong as you think
you are, big booty girl.
Who the fuck do you think
you're talking to?
Okay!
- Because you're su...
- Shut the fuck up!
Don't "shush" me.
- So fucking..
- Hey...
Sometimes I look at you, and I beat
your face into a little pulp.
Your little mouth.
Your stupid smile.
That voice.
Hey, stop doing that.
You'll hurt yourself.
Douching is for amateurs.
Do we need to tie you up again?
C'mon go back to sleep.
Good.
Goddamn slut!
You're a bunch of common criminals,
petty thugs.
My crime was the only one
worthy of the name.
Even up here,
black-uns are the first to go.
Are you sick?
You wanna clog the machine,
is that what you want!?
She want it.
Don't do that!
You sick!
It's what god wants.
Don't ever do that again.
Stay away.
Fuck your baby mission.
Your hormones are fucking bullshit.
It's our willpower
that kills the foetuses.
It's a stroke.
Don't tell anyone.
Shit, the report!
He was fucked.
Maybe we were fucked too.
The mission.
Everything.
9149, daily progress report.
All systems in full functional mode.
All crew members are complying
with mission experiments.
Over and out.
It's time for lights out.
♪ Always alone ♪
♪ Alone and blue ♪
♪ I've got no one ♪
♪ To share my troubles to ♪
♪ No one to care ♪
♪ To call my own ♪
♪ Seems I must always be alone. ♪
There is nothing to fear.
I promise.
Everything's gonna be fine.
I have no one to help me
like I'm helping you.
No one to put me out of my misery.
I remain alone with my guilt.
Huh? What? What?
What?
Suck my dick.
Please.
Hey! What are you doing?
Let me go, you fucker!
Stop it!
Help meeee!
Leave her alone!
Help! Help!
Get off her!
Help! Heeelp!
Shut up!
Come on, take this off!
Broke my nose!
I will kill that motherfucker.
Fuck outa here!
C'mon.
Fuckin' walk!
Wanna carry me?
Not so easy to get
inside of you, is it?
My body obeys me.
It's good.
I'll never have kids.
Sure of that.
OK, breathe.
Did you really kill your own kids?
You suffocated them?
In their little beds?
With their little pillows?
And your husband?
With a knife.
I would have killed myself.
I tried.
This made your plastic pussy.
Dibs increased the dose
when she wanted us at her mercy.
We'd all hit the wall
and dropped like flies.
Sleep, for hours.
Sleep.
I'm the pilot.
You cannot make me sleep.
Sleep.
Yes my arms so good.
Matty...
Maybe it's because you never
wanted anything from me.
I'm about to have you now.
Why don't you ever take me
in your arms?
If I close my eyes,
I know I'm gonna feel you inside.
You know.
I almost can feel it.
Yes.
Fill me.
Fill me, Marty.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Here.
Yes.
Grow into her, baby.
Grow inside.
My baby.
They caught me.
My good baby.
C'mon. Hey.
C'mon, get out.
I hate that bed.
C'mon!
Go back to your own bunkbed.
C'mon.
C'mon. Too heavy now.
Crazy girl.
It's too far.
Bums and losers.
That's what you are.
I found all your records.
You killed your friend over a dog.
Yeah.
My crazy girl.
Do I detect a farewell in your eyes?
Skilled pilot.
None of the rest of us
could do this.
You made your choice.
Why're you crying?
I have to stay alone now.
Where we going?
To the garden.
That's not Nansen.
That's not Nansen!
It's Boyse!
Twik!
The child is your daughter.
One of your genes.
She's strong made.
Like her big pudding mother.
For me, she's perfection.
"I'd rather sink into the Earth,"
"after I've lost you than
to sit around and grieve,"
"unless you've gone off
onto your destiny."
What're you talking about?
It's what my wife told me.
I told her I was doing all this
for her and our son.
To turn our shame
into some type of glory, y'know.
She says that this mission,
was like burning her twice
and that my idea of glory
was bullshit.
It's no response.
It looks like ours.
It's the same.
It's the same ship.
There might be ahh..
other..
people..
on board.
So?
What?
They might be able
to help us, ahh...
We don't need help.
Are you scared?
- No.
- No?
Are you sure?
Are those.. dogs?
Yeah.
You help the baby dog?
I had to leave it.
Why didn't you take it?
We could have kept it.
Couldn't, captain.
I wanted a dog so bad.
A little dog, to hold.
You know why.
Please step away from the door,
it wasn't clean in there.
Gotta disinfect,
gotta clean myself.
It'll die in there.
It's cruelty!
Whadda you know about cruelty?
Dunno anything about it.
I need to clean,
I need to disinfect myself..
Move away from the door.
Move away from the door!
Get out.
You were right, dad.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I have everything I need here.
Screw up, Pena.
What're you doin'?
Praying.
You know what god to pray to?
What god are you praying to?
I saw it in some
of the random images from Earth.
I just.. wanted to know
what they feel.
Time to feed the dog.
ID 149.
Local day:
Earth days:
It looks like a, crocodile's eye.
More like a mouth
that wants to swallow us up.
So big.
We should try it.
I can feel it.
Oh you can feel it?
I thought we were supposed
to be drifters.
But it's so big!
I feel the density
is very low.
I believe in this one.
I'm sad that you leave
all your data.
Even your prison records.
You might have been a criminal,
but you're a hero to me.
All be destroyed by the firewall
once the ship gets sucked
into the black hole anyway.
There is no firewall. I know it.
We'll make it through.
You always avoid my questions.
Do I look like my mother?
No.
Take good look.
My eyes?
No.
My hair?
No not at all.
My nose?
My mouth?
No, you have rodent teeth.
Yer little rat.
Rats are incredibly
intelligent animals.
Am I weird looking?
You're special.
So different.
You're like no one else.
And I love that.
Shall we?
Yes.